<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CityBeautiful</string>
    <string name="my_city">Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="category_tourist">Tourist Places</string>
    <string name="category_restaurant">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_college">Colleges</string>
    <string name="category_event">Events</string>

    <string name="event_first_head">Rose Festival</string>
    <string name="event_first_detail">The Rose Festival of Chandigarh is one of the
                biggest rose shows held in India. The venue is the famous Zakir Hussein Rose Garden
                situated in the city of Chandigarh. The garden has over 50000 rose plants and
                bushes of more than 825 varieties</string>
    <string name="event_first_location">Sector 12</string>

    <string name="event_second_head">PEC Fest</string>
    <string name="event_second_detail">When the city descends on the campus of PEC to
                dance to the tunes of Groovz and Bhangratheque, swoon over Glitterati, chorus
                to the tunes of Coke Studio and dance along Sunburn, you can be sure of one thing,
                the sound drown out everything else in Chandigarh.</string>
    <string name="event_second_location">Sector 14</string>

    <string name="event_third_head">Mango Mela</string>
    <string name="event_third_detail">An annual event, the Mango Mela is organized in
                the month of  July ,is a treat for the lovers of the king of fruits, mango.
                Hundreds of varieties of mangoes from as far as Maharasthra, Bihar,
                Uttar Pradesh and also from Haryana, Himachal and Punjab arrive here,
                delighting everyone with their hybrid shapes and quality.</string>
    <string name="event_third_location">Pinjore</string>

    <string name="event_fourth_head">Grub Fest</string>
    <string name="event_fourth_detail">The Grub Fest is India biggest food festival with
                the best restaurants displaying their signature delicacies over some good music
                and hearty performances to keep you entertained. Take in the aromas, try out
                interesting cuisines, fill your baskets with unique gourmet products</string>
    <string name="event_fourth_location">Sector 17</string>

    <string name="event_fifth_head">Chandigarh Carnival</string>
    <string name="event_fifth_detail">The carnival consist of stalls exhibited
                by various academies, NGOs and government departments who have displayed various
                art and craft in different stalls, day-long cultural programmes by various
                artists/performer on stage, amusement park, joy rides and camel rides for
                kids, along with various fun and frolic activities and presence of cartoon
                characters during the event.</string>
    <string name="event_fifth_location">Sector 10</string>


    <string name="tourist_first_head">Rock Garden</string>
    <string name="tourist_first_detail">A symbol of imagination and novelty, this one is of
                its kind of garden spread across an area of 64 acres. The Rock Garden has been
                designed as an open air exhibition hall using urban and industrial
                wastes by Nek Chand, a former Road Inspector in Chandigarh.</string>
    <string name="tourist_first_location">Sector 1</string>

    <string name="tourist_second_head">Sukhna Lake</string>
    <string name="tourist_second_detail">Nestled at the foothills of Shivaliks, Sukhna Lake
                is a beautiful lake set amid the picturesque surroundings. Quite popular amid
                the locals and visitors, the place is a perfect destination for solitude seekers</string>
    <string name="tourist_second_location">Sector 1</string>

    <string name="tourist_third_head">Rose Garden</string>
    <string name="tourist_third_detail">Rose garden, located at 16 sector of Chandigarh is
                a place to relax amid the nature at its best. The garden is packed with some
                exquisite variety of flowers making it quite popular among tourists and
                nature enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="tourist_third_location">Sector 16</string>

    <string name="tourist_fourth_head">Fun City</string>
    <string name="tourist_fourth_detail">Located on an expanse of 43 acres, this water amusement
                park in Ramgarh is the biggest in North India. It boasts of one activity pool,
                three landing pools and a wave pool, a cluster of water slides of various shapes
                and sizes, which makes for a delightful ride for the water lovers.</string>
    <string name="tourist_fourth_location">Ramgarh</string>

    <string name="tourist_fifth_head">Pinjore Garden</string>
    <string name="tourist_fifth_detail">Spread over a massive area of 100 acres and
                also known as Yadvinder Garden, Pinjore Garden is a spectacle to behold.</string>
    <string name="tourist_fifth_location">Pinjore</string>

    <string name="tourist_sixth_head">Bougainvillea Garden</string>
    <string name="tourist_sixth_detail">With fifty varieties of bougainvillea on
                display, this garden established in 1976 is spread over 20 acres.
                Its popularity lies in its varied shaped bougainvilleas- arch, pavilions, a cluster
                of bowers, and arcades. The annual Bougainvillea festival is a major draw here.</string>
    <string name="tourist_sixth_location">Sector 2</string>

    <string name="tourist_seventh_head">International Dolls Muesuem</string>
    <string name="tourist_seventh_detail">Founded in the year 1985 by the
                Indian Council of Child Welfare, the museum contains a wide collection of
                fascinating dolls and marionettes brought from countries like Germany, Denmark,
                Netherlands, Spain,Korea, and Russia that stand beside the huge Indian collection.</string>
    <string name="tourist_seventh_location">Sector 23</string>

    <string name="tourist_eighth_head">Children Traffic Park</string>
    <string name="tourist_eighth_detail">Replete with real-life road scenarios, the Children Traffic
                Park in Sector 23A has extensive traffic control mechanisms such as road bents,
                inclines and declines, overpass, underpass, parallel parking area, blind alley,
                and uncontrolled intersections, T-Intersections, Stop Signs and Blinkers.</string>
    <string name="tourist_eighth_location">Sector 23A</string>

    <string name="tourist_ninth_head">Garden of Fragnance</string>
    <string name="tourist_ninth_detail">Garden of Fragrance as the name suggests is
                famous for its fragrant plants such as Mehndi, Haar Shingar, Raat ki Rani, Motia,
                Champa, demask rose and varieties of jasmine. The park with beautiful landscape
                also offers a delightful walk for its visitors.</string>
    <string name="tourist_ninth_location">Sector 36</string>


    <string name="college_first_detail">Panjab University is a public collegiate
                university located in Chandigarh, India. It originated in 1882,
                but was established in 1947, making it one of the oldest universities in India.</string>
    <string name="college_second_detail">Punjab Engineering College, is an engineering institute
                located in the city of Chandigarh, India. Founded in 1921,
                it is one of the oldest educational institutes in India</string>
    <string name="college_third_detail">Mehr Chand Mahajan DAV College for Women,
                Chandigarh popularly known as MCM DAV, was established in 1968
                by the DAV College Managing Committee</string>
    <string name="college_fourth_detail">Chitkara University in Punjab has been
                founded by Dr.Ashok Chitkara and Dr.Madhu Chitkara who have been passionate
                teachers for more than 40 years now.</string>
    <string name="college_fifth_detail">The institution was incepted on 3rd July,
                1973 in the revered memory of Goswami Ganesh Dutta Ji, who envisioned Chandigarh
                as a focal point of culture and saw it as a potential hub
                for Sanatanist activities.</string>
    <string name="college_sixth_detail">Chandigarh Group of Colleges Landran has
                been a pioneer of world class education in the past decade and a half, having
                developed with state of the art facilities.</string>
    <string name="college_seventh_detail">Established in October 1959, CSIO was chartered to
                stimulate the growth of indigenous instrument industry in the country through
                development of contemporary technologies and other scientific
                technological assistance.</string>

    <string name="college_first_head">Punjab University</string>
    <string name="college_second_head">PEC</string>
    <string name="college_third_head">MCM DAV</string>
    <string name="college_fourth_head">Chitkara University</string>
    <string name="college_fifth_head">SD College</string>
    <string name="college_sixth_head">CGC Landran</string>
    <string name="college_seventh_head">CSIO</string>

    <string name="college_first_location">Sector 14</string>
    <string name="college_second_location">Sector 12</string>
    <string name="college_third_location">Sector 36A</string>
    <string name="college_fourth_location">Baddi</string>
    <string name="college_fifth_location">Sector 32</string>
    <string name="college_sixth_location">Landran</string>
    <string name="college_seventh_location">Sector 31</string>


    <string name="restaurant_first_head">Nik Bakers</string>
    <string name="restaurant_second_head">Whistling Duck</string>
    <string name="restaurant_third_head">Hops And Grains</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fourth_head">Monicas</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fifth_head">Pal Dhaba</string>
    <string name="restaurant_sixth_head">Brooklyn Center</string>
    <string name="restaurant_seventh_head">The Beer Cafe</string>
    <string name="restaurant_eighth_head">Kingdom Of Beer</string>


    <string name="restaurant_first_detail">For those of you who love baked treats, this
                place is a must-visit and they have plenty on offer. You can drop by for a quick
                nibble of quiches and tarts, or have a hearty meal of burgers, sandwiches,
                pizzas and pastas.\nMeal for two: Rs:1,500</string>
    <string name="restaurant_second_detail">If you love big spaces, ample sunlight and
                community tables, then the Whistling Duck is the best option, particularly for
                Sunday brunch. The menu offers a global fare, from gyozas, gnocchi, pork chops
                and burgers to malai tikkas and keema pao.
                \nMeal for two: Rs:3,500</string>
    <string name="restaurant_third_detail">The first microbrewery in the city, from the outside
                it may seem ordinary but as you step in, the chic interiors and the vibe of the
                place are sure to turn up your energy levels.
                \nMeal for two: Rs 3000</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fourth_detail">This quaint bakery may fool you with its
                size, but it offers some spectacular cakes and pastries. It is one of the oldest
                in town, and has a loyal fan following.
                \nMeal for two: Rs:800</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fifth_detail">Away from all the modernistic structures, stands the
                humble Pal Dhaba, one of the oldest eateries in the city. A look at their hall of
                fame and you learn that it is immensely popular among Bollywood celebs too.
                \nMeal for two: Rs:800</string>
    <string name="restaurant_sixth_detail">Located in the courtyard at Elante Mall, this
                American-style resto-bar is popular with the locals. The urban industrial set-up
                teamed with simple décor creates a casual space to catch up with friends for
                a drink or a fun lunch.\nMeal for two: Rs 3000</string>
   <string name="restaurant_eighth_detail">Great Place to enjoy with friends and family
       \nMeal for two: Rs 2500 </string>


    <string name="restaurant_first_location">Sector 35</string>
    <string name="restaurant_second_location">Sector 26</string>
    <string name="restaurant_third_location">Sector 36A</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fourth_location">Sector 35</string>
    <string name="restaurant_fifth_location">Sector 28</string>
    <string name="restaurant_sixth_location">Elante Mall</string>
    <string name="restaurant_seventh_location">Elante Mall</string>
    <string name="restaurant_eighth_location">Sector 8</string>






</resources>
